Every chapter of Nekros
that the crimes were based on…
is from the same user.
The name is…
Asura.
I’m just the messenger.
It got me thinking
that the person who doesn’t want
this nonsense to end
is you.
You’re not a cop or a reporter.
What you are is just a brat!
I’m just a useless thing to you.
You don’t believe in me at all.
(Inspector Yotsaphat Traikanawut.)
(This was also the surname
of Commissioner Praphaphat,)
(the Inspector’s very own father.)
You knew all this time, didn’t you?
Your father destroyed my family.
The reason I chose to be a cop
was because I wanted to remind myself
that I would never make
the same mistake my father did.
(You’re not a cop or a reporter.)
What you are is just a brat!
Yeah!
I’m just a useless thing to you.
You don’t believe in me at all.
(Chapter 20 really is intense.)
(But if the next victim
really is in Chapter 20,)
(that means there isn’t
just one murderer.)
Who helped you come up with the methods?
I’m just the messenger.
I don’t know…
But if that’s the case,
it’s interesting, isn’t it?
I think…
Kim is just a pawn.
Someone is working behind the curtain,
pulling the strings and helping him.
The number 20 Kim wrote on the glass…
It’s no coincidence.
I think it’s the clue to the next victim,
which is in Chapter 20 of Nekros.
Right now, Praew is helping me
look for the rest of the manga
from the Nekros fans
in an underground blog.
If we get those,
we might get some more clues.
The police did everything you told us to.
But every information we have…
is what you already saw.
I don’t think there’s a Nekros fan
who wants to help the police out
more than I do.
If you don’t believe me, that’s okay.
I’ll keep digging either way.
Are you here for the interview?
Yes.
I’ll fetch the boss.
Wait.
The victim in Chapter 20
is the mafia who gets away with
murdering an entire family of witnesses.
Since it’s a high-profile case,
I think it won’t be hard to find him.
(I got it.)
(This must be him.)
(Kamjorn Petchchai,
also known as Big Brother Piaw.)
(I’ll send you the link.)
“Prosecutor family murder case concluded:”
“Court dismisses contract killing charge.”
Attorney Komkrit was Piaw’s lawyer?
(I heard Piaw has a logistic
and recruitment company now.)
If he’s not the victim in Chapter 20,
I don’t think anyone is.
Oh, you’re on time.
Hello. Hello.
I’m sorry we have to
schedule you at this time.
I’m a busy man. I can hardly find time.
It’s quite alright.
We barely gave you any notice.
Don’t worry about that.
Why don’t we talk in my office?
I had my staff prepare
some drinks and snacks for you.
It’s too hot out here.
Let’s talk in my office where it’s cool.
Please come in.
(Kaye. I got Chapter 20.)
“PLEASE DON’T HURT ME.”
“HEY.”
“HOW COME A PIG LIKE YOU CAN TALK?”
(Prim and I are going to his company
to investigate this.)
(Once we know anything,
I’ll keep you updated.)
PROSECUTOR FAMILY MURDER CASE CONCLUDED:
COURT DISMISSES CONTRACT KILLING CHARGE.
I’ve been through a lot
before I am where I am today,
from bathroom masseur
to valet parking attendant.
We didn’t know that.
You need to tell us more about that.
Of course. I will tell you.
-Sir.
-I’ve been through—
Thank you, sir.
For what?
The pizza.
You ordered us some pizza, right?
Me?
Yes.
I did?
Maybe they got the wrong place.
But go on and enjoy it. My treat.
Yes, sir.
Let’s go.
My employees are probably
just playing some games.
Don’t worry about it.
Tell them to pipe down a little.
We have guests today.
Yes, sir.
Let’s keep going.
Come on.
Hey, man.
KAYE
Kaye, what’s up?
You’re getting good at hiding.
But I’m here to collect my interest today!
Kaye?
Where are you?
Kaye!
When I was working as a valet,
all I could do was look at these rich men
leaving their cars with me.
I remember thinking
I wanted to be just like them one day.
Now that I’m here, in hindsight,
I can barely believe
I brought myself here.
You’re really amazing, sir.
Thank you.
Oh!
Oh, you’ve made a mess.
I’m going to the bathroom to clean up.
Of course.
Just out the door to the right,
at the end of the hallway.
Don’t wander off.
You might get lost.
My office is quite big, after all.
Your story is very fun.
I’ll come back for it.
Of course.
Go on.
Guys, let’s get this load over with
before we eat.
Come on.
PHAT
I’ll take a little break
to check up on my office.
I have to see
if my staff manage the place neatly.
Where was I in the story?
Right, right, right…
The world is cruel.
(First of all,)
(you need to stop being scared.)
See clearly.
(Don’t look away.)
(If you do,)
(you won’t see your enemy.)
(And you won’t see his openings.)
(Let your body navigate the flow.)
(Focus on the opponent in front of you.)
(Twist your hips
and swing your leg like a bat.)
(Take deep breaths.)
(When they’re not looking,
elbow them really hard.)
Shut up!
Get in there!
You decoys.
Who sent you?
We really are journalists.
We’re working on
the Nekros serial murders.
I know you’d be the next victim
so we’re here to warn yo—
Shush!
Nonsense!
Nerve…
You have some nerve.
Don’t you?
Take these two to a separate room.
Tell our client I have
two extra merchandise for them for free.
It’s freaking exclusive.
Yes, sir.
Go! Get up!
Get up!
Go!
Kaye!
What happened?
Hey, stay with me.
Stay with me.
I’ll take you to the hospital.
No…
No, Phat.
Look at you, dude!
Phat, listen to me.
Right now, Praew…
She’s in danger.
Thanks.
I finally got the information
on the victim Praew sent me.
The victim is…
Kamjorn Petchchai.
Oh, that jerk!
I know him.
He has endless charges to his name.
I’m an idiot.
I know damn well what my sister is like,
and I said that to her.
It was my fault, too.
I didn’t think it through,
and dragged your sister into this.
But Praew also sent me
the location of the victim’s office.
Okay. I bet that’s where she is.
You have some nerve, huh?
Don’t hurt my friend, you asshole!
Prim.
Stay out of the way.
If it’s not your turn yet,
then, it’s not your business!
It’s not your business.
You bitch, you bit me!
How dare you bite me!
You dare bite me?
I said stay out of the way!
This is only for fooling me.
But don’t you worry.
I’ll sell you both eventually.
But right now, I just want to beat you up
until I’m satisfied.
You’re a biter, huh?
You’re a biter, huh!
Your turn now.
Run. Run.
Keep running.
Lay there and stay still,
and I’ll give you a show.
Halt!
Police!
What’s wrong with him?
Nop.
Contact local police
and call an ambulance.
Tell them to come to Bangkok Worker
Company as fast as possible.
There are multiple deaths,
likely from poisoning.
Praew.
Praew!
Praew. Praew.
(Kim’s death in solitary raises questions
regarding police’s security.)
(On a more interesting note,
social media has picked up a connection,)
(pointed out By Mr. Thun of Thun Insight,)
(who has dug up the connection
between all all Nekros victims)
(to the high-profile
Thai Investment Bank case)
(from 20 years ago.)
(This might be more than
what we thought were murder cases.)
I’ll turn the TV off.
That connection of the victims
to the Thai Investment Bank
that the reporter was saying…
That is true.
Before this, I looked through
the information of all four victims.
The businessman,
the Permanent Secretary,
the lawyer,
and MP Jaratphong.
Their names are all
in the Thai Investment Bank case file
from 20 years ago.
Some of them were witnesses,
some enablers,
and some got acquitted
because of the loopholes in the laws.
Yeah…
I just realized that all the chapters
the murderers chose to imitate
and all the victims…
are all information
from a user named Asura.
I don’t think it’s a coincidence.
I’ve been trying to contact Asura
for a while now,
but so far there’s no response.
-Hello.
-Hello, Uncle.
I’ll go.
I want you to keep taking your time off.
Take it as a holiday.
You’ve been working hard long enough.
And more importantly…
Praew needs you in a time like this.
Yes, sir.
Don’t worry about the case.
I have men looking for Piaw right now.
He will pay for what he did.
TITLE: NEKROS CHAPTER 20
“BIG BROTHER P. IS THE DEVIL
IN HUMAN DISGUISE.”
How is Praew doing?
Is she doing better?
No.
The doctor said her body is okay,
but her mind might not be.
They said she might be
experiencing dissociation.
Dissociation…
What is that?
It’s an automatic mechanism
against stress.
In extremely stressful situations,
the body shuts down.
Even when she wakes up,
she might not remember some moments.
I’m here to visit her.
I’m here to visit Prim as well,
so I thought I’d stop by to see Praew.
I’m sorry for what happened.
Your sister is a promising
young girl, Inspector—
Just shut the fuck up.
It’s because of you that she’s like this.
I never asked anyone
to do anything like this.
Prim and Praew did what they did
because they really believe in it.
It’s okay.
It doesn’t matter.
I understand how awful you must be feeling
being unable to protect your sister.
-Phat.
-Listen to him!
What the hell did you say?
Phat, calm down.
Calm down.
I think you should leave.
Excuse me, then.
Tell the team to get ready.
We’re changing our plan.
We’ll focus on Piaw’s case.
Our staff won’t get hurt in vain.
I’ll let everyone judge those scums.
We’re burning them to the ground tonight.
Phat.
-Fuck!
-Phat, you jerk!
Damn it!
Phat, listen to me!
Take it easy.
Listen to me.
Listen.
This won’t help with anything.
You’re only making it worse for yourself.
I…
I’m sorry about your sister.
I just want to tell you that…
you’re already doing a good job
as a brother.
As a cop, as well.
Yes, Nop.
(Inspector, we got a lead on Piaw.)
I’m suspended right now.
(You should come anyway, sir.)
(I sent you the coordinate.)
This is the house of the prosecutor
whose whole family was murdered.
Does it look like the one in your manga?
Yes.
Oh, Inspector Phat.
What are you doing here?
I heard you were suspended by your uncle.
I got an order to take over this case.
Come on.
No need to look so serious.
Let’s take turns proving ourselves.
I need a big break, too, you know?
Nop.
Escort everyone who’s not involved
out of the area.
Secure the crime scene,
and don’t let anyone touch the evidence.
It’s alright, Nop.
I was already on my way out.
Sorry for intruding.
As the manga creator,
you’re still the prime suspect.
See?
This proves that it’s all Nekros’ doing.
Kim was just a pawn.
The real murderer is still out there.
The prosecutor’s family was murdered here.
Everyone in his family was Christian.
It coincides with Piaw’s death
in Chapter 20.
Dying in a bathtub
indicates an unholy baptism.
The baptism of death.
The murderer chose to wash Piaw’s sins
with water and blood.
And the torn out page of the psalms…
That is Psalm 25,
which is the story of David’s plea to God,
asking for forgiveness.
The torn out page is a symbol
that God denies that plea.
And I think Chapter 25—
About that…
Let Kitti and his team deal with it.
What does that mean?
I’m no longer leading this investigation,
and I’m not getting involved again.
And you need to be careful.
Kitti still thinks
you’re the prime suspect.
Didn’t I prove myself
that I had nothing to do with Piaw’s case?
I’ve been telling you
there isn’t just one murderer.
That’s exactly why.
It makes you even
more suspicious than before.
Did you know that there’s
a type of murderer called a mastermind?
The one who controls everything.
He wouldn’t get his hands bloodied,
but pull the strings with psychology
from behind the curtain.
He borrows someone else’s hands
to do his dirty work.
At least that’s what any police
in this world would think.
Your visiting him that day
wasn’t so you could get some clues,
but it was for you to say your last words
or release him from his duty.
Let him die
just to cut his tie to you, his prophet.
What do you think?
Do you think I’m the murderer?
(I’ve got all the chapters of Nekros.)
(I’m sorry I saved them.)
(It’s just… I really loved the manga.)
(Is it possible to meet you just once?)
(I’ll give you all the chapters.)
(I’ll wait for you
at Benice Pub & Bistro until midnight.)
Mr. Kaye.
What a small world.
Mr. Thun.
Yes.
It’s me.
Show me your hand.
Just show me.
You didn’t have to do this.
But you’re bleeding.
There.
All done.
Don’t stress about it.
I understand what it feels like…
to be left behind all alone.
I don’t want you to go through that.
Thanks, bud…
For being here.
Maybe Asura is the shadow
trailing behind you all this time…
You just never know it.
You’re me.
I’m you.
No one knows you better than I do.
Shut up!
I’m not you!
Just let me out.
The world needs Nekros.
The world needs someone
to wipe out those assholes…
Those scums.
Kaye, run.
Run!
Did I kill him, Phat?
You’re not a murderer.
I’m going to find out who is behind this.